

NISHA MORE

FRONT-END ENGINEER

My Contact

nisha.more.2909@gmail.com

+917972630959

🗣 Nashik, Maharashtra, India

https://github.com/nishamore98

in www.linkedin.com/in/nishamore98/

https://nishamore.tech/

Skills

HTML 5

CSS

scss

MUI

JavaScript

Redux

ReactJS

Bootstrap

Agile

NPM

Tools

Figma

Jira

GIT & GitHub

VS Code

Postman

Soft Skills

Creative

Communication Skills

Team building

Adaptive

Problem solving

Collaborative

Education Background

Matoshri College Of Engineering and Research center, Nashik - B.E. Electrical
 JUNE 2018 - AUG 2021
 CGPA - 7.46

Projects

-Smart mask vending machine and thermal body temperature monitoring, alert system with automatic sanitiser

-Dual input inverter (Solar & AC)

 K.K Wagh Women's Polytechnic, Nashik-Diploma in Electronics and Telecommunication
 JULY 2014 - JUNE 2018 CGPA - 7

About Me

A highly skilled front end software developer with 1.5 years of experience in developing and designing user-friendly websites and web applications. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and frameworks such as React and Redux. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to work well in a team.

Professional Experience

ITILITE Technologies - Frontend Engineer Nov 2021 - Feb 2023

Key responsibilities

- Created visually appealing and responsive user interfaces for the feature Client admin as behalf approver that provided a seamless user experience across various devices and platforms.
 200+ Users has given good feedback about the feature.
- Built the feature of transferring roles of users on deactivation.
 This feature led to a significant increase of 30% in user engagement also contributed in revenue growth.
- Built various reusable UI components and Published NPM packages. Successfully integrated third-party services into the system.
- Worked closely with designers, stakeholders and engineers to
 ensure that the design specifications for the feature Time based
 policy, document handler and admin notifications for new login
 request are accurately implemented in the user interface.
- Created User profile page and Help and support page using jsx, scss, React and ensuring cross-browser compatibility, performance, and accessibility.
- Participating in Agile development processes, including sprint planning, stand-up meetings, and retrospectives. Contributed in peer to peer code reviews and mentored interns in their tasks.

ITILITE Technologies - Intern Frontend Engineer Aug 2021 - Oct 2021

Key responsibilities

- Image optimisation to improve website performance
- Created UI for showing YouTube video inside the modal
- Made UI changes & add anchors in existing UI
- Studied about React, created Test Route & Component
- Used react-data-table library to show data
- API integration
- Created UI for Help & Support page
- Created To Do list

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Marathi